[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The clerics demanded talks with local US commanders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"demanded\", does the participant \"clerics\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i have a baby eastern king snake .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" You say , ' wow ! '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A sender purporting to be islamist sent cyanide in both early 2002 and early 2003 in New Zealand and ingredients of nerve gas in Belgium in 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"sender\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I experienced a Definite Decrease in food craving ( about 50 % ) and decrease in stress after the 1st treatment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"experienced\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We believe it addresses many of the issues and concerns you have raised in the workshops .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raised\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A Yellowstone wolf was found dead , hit by a car , on a Colorado highway last year , several hundred miles from home .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"wolf\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It has two parts , both of which are timed for 90 seconds each and the differential between the resulting two scores determines the likelihood of having a learning disability or attention deficit disorder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"timed\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The first time I used them they arrived on time and towed car for me to the destination I needed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"towed\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( We check in early afternoon and we fly next day . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fly\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" All you have to do is look at the photographs , \" Ed Bangs , wolf recovery coordinator for the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service , told UPI 's Blue Planet ,\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Bangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Debbie said , it is going to be hard on me to sale my old dodge truck .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sale\", does the participant \"truck\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have 4 Golden Wonder Killifish .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Killifish\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think they may even be better than the pair I have been using this past year !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"they have their own website which you can easily find using any search engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"website\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dismissed\", does the participant \"government\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They said they were \" unable to tell me until they ordered my dress \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"dress\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the participant \"staff\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"To the north in Lebanon , there is serious debate within Hezbollah about entering the Lebanese political process in light of Syria 's promised withdrawal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"entering\", does the participant \"process\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think 90 percent of the tenants are smokers !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the participant \"Marathon\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" The information transmitted is intended only for the person or entity to which it is addressed and may contain confidential and / or privileged material .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"addressed\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the participant \"face\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Abdel Rahman 's son was captured in Quetta , Pakistan in mid-February 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"captured\", does the participant \"son\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"TEXAS ROADHOUSE HAS VERY GOOD MEALS , THAT THE MEAT COMES RIGHT OFF THE BONES .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAS\", does the participant \"MEALS\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Olympus X - 940 14 Megapixel Digital Camera has filters and can do all sorts of special effects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Camera\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Secretive efforts keep outsiders in the dark about the program 's goals\"\nQuestion: In the event \"keep\", does the participant \"outsiders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe you got a copy of the John Sommer letter to producers dated Jan 6 that MKM 's spies intercepted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My first three children were born in Southern Ontario cities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"children\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On my panel , Loretta Lynch asked Reliant and Duke to supply her with the details of the contracts they cut to sell their power forward to marketers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cut\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I purchased a 2 - year old certified pre-owned BMW from this dealership .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"BMW\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The last wolf was killed in Yellowstone National Park in 1943 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"wolf\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We respect the fact that debate and discussion continue in many of our religious communities as to the scriptural , theological and liturgical issues involved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continue\", does the participant \"debate\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had my wedding luncheon at this BJ s restaurant , and it was one of the best choices that I made .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"luncheon\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They showed some kids on TV , and they were quite taken with it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it s only fair that nowadays every town should provide at least one halal cafe or restaurant and hopefully one day every British catering establishment will be halal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The future president joined the Guard in May 1968 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Guard\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sussexs have soft feathers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"feathers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The plain fact is that a few members of IT are pushing this initiative , but they lack commercial sponsorship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pushing\", does the participant \"members\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I use propane with a blower and a burner I built http://www.mikegigi.com/meltmetl.htm and http://www.mikegigi.com/firehole.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Nobody thinks that there will be a lot of oil and gas in this part of the world , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I found my initial selection satisfactory but the wine flight we chose to be poorly composed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"chose\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think that this is for you since I do n't know any of these people .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I interviewed several contractors for a kitchen remodel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interviewed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" They can freely write anything they like about our prophet , but if one raises doubts about the Holocaust he is either fined or sent to prison , \" he added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the participant \"one\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last month , Nasrallah announced that his party would close ranks with Hamas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"announced\", does the participant \"Nasrallah\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checking\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We feed the chickens scraps of veggies and fruits throughout the day , but it 's nothing that a rabbit would n't be able to digest just fine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"feed\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is our belief that this compensation plan will produce some of the largest checks in network marketing history .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"some\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I played dumb and asked him questions that I already knew the answers to and he responded with half truths and a few falsehoods .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"responded\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accumulate\", does the participant \"minimum\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" We wish them a successful return of their astronauts . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A key question is how they acquired the anthrax strain first isolated by the Texas Veterinary Medical Diagnostic Lab in 1980 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"acquired\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The only neurological sign that he shows is that he barely drags his toes and sometimes has trouble with his right lead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"sign\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Terry said he made that filing in the interest of Californians , but I find that argument has no basis in fact . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Terry\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Our system reflects SJ Bondad GDP but SWG is going to pay us based on SJ Non-Bondad GDP .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"animals\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In our Constitutional system , we have three branches of the Federal Government : the Legislative , Executive , and Judicial branches .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Sufaat was arrested in December 2001 upon his return to Malaysia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I need to have a form filled out that says I do n't have health insurance coverage through Enron .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jam\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like to imagine the thought processes going on in W 's head if he were to actually read the letter , but it is hard to picture him actually reading this letter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picture\", does the participant \"him\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We intend to see as many people as possible regarding EOL implementation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"intend\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bangs said these animals are not equipped to survive in the wild , however , and they all almost certainly have died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Colombo held six rounds of talks with the Tigers between September 2002 and March 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"held\", does the participant \"Colombo\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Each provincial government has a website that lists the process for that Province so depending upon where you were born you can google it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"google\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We took our 7 month old and she laughed and giggled when ( very harshly I might add ) grabbing and ' kissed ' the goats and lambs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"add\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Kori told me she saw you last night at Steak Night and introduced herself since I failed to do so the last time we went .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduced\", does the participant \"herself\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Some conservationists want the protection extended so wolves can move into other states , including Colorado , Utah and Oregon , among others .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"protection\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"patience\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I guess you get what you pay for .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Al Qaeda had a motive in mind .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"Qaeda\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cover letters and resumes need to be perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"letters\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We are resolved that the State should not interfere with same - gender couples who choose to marry and share fully and equally in the rights , responsibilities , and commitments of civil marriage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"resolved\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin said up to 80 % of the city was submerged , in some cases by waters 6 m ( 20 ft ) deep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"submerged\", does the participant \"%\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I wish all happy holidays , and moreso , peace on earth .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"holidays\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This means that messages initiated at Corp and intended for the entire Enron organization will not reach any business units outside the Corp domain .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the participant \"This\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i knew someone in college who had one and i loved it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i have a 1 and a half year old male neutered cat and a new 2 month old spayed female kitten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I assume his actual reason is that he 's worried that Berkshire Hathaway just ca n't grow quickly enough to justify his usual charity policy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assume\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I doubt you will get a sensible answer in the \" TRAVEL \" section .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"doubt\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Pakistani press reported that she was nabbed in Karachi after being spotted at the airport in late March or early April 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"nabbed\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" It may be uninteresting to a lot of people , \" Beschta told Blue Planet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Beschta\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Musharraf calls the bluff\"\nQuestion: In the event \"calls\", does the participant \"Musharraf\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I survived it without a problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"survived\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"But today , I got a boy and realized that he is HUGE !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"boy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Records show that on Oct. 31 , power generators and electricity traders filed letters with the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission , demanding that the new plan be killed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"generators\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We elected to not do the EPM test because there was NO neurological signs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"elected\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have 5 sisters and so including my mom ... he is the only guy in a house of six females .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"sisters\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I got a riding lesson today on one of my boss 's fino horses and it made me realize just how unsteady my left leg is .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Miramar was founded September 20 1888 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"founded\", does the participant \"Miramar\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Guerrillas near Hawijah launched an attack that left 6 dead , including 4 Iraqi soldiers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launched\", does the participant \"Guerrillas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think Valerie Mooney ( our credit person ) and Ed Sacks are still discussing some minor fine tuning of the LOC format .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I assume you need both gas and power .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assume\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He and his master dragged me to my room and held judgment upon me as a convicted traitress .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dragged\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Well , they have a variety of sports that they play like basketball , soccer , etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"variety\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need a background in law enforcement .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"background\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You have two adjustment screws for up and down and right to left positions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"screws\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We oppose the use of sacred texts and religious traditions to deny legal equity to same - gender couples .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deny\", does the participant \"equity\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Several candidates were assassinated and targeted these last two weeks , others have been forced under threats to withdraw and to follow the example of the Islamic party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"candidates\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Lo and behold , they replaced the screen ( which had to be ordered ) yesterday and did n't charge me a dime .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charge\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Cj and company did all that we ask and 10 times more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Cj\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"named\", does the participant \"Holinshed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"All of the doors tend to look alike and having ' something ' on your door helps you and your kids find your room easier .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tend\", does the participant \"All\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They asked us things that we would have never have thought of , and took extra time to meet with us when we needed it before the wedding .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know you are very worried , but getting her to the vet is the best thing you can do for her .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"These links present the many viewpoints that existed and still exist about the disaster called Chernobyl :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"present\", does the participant \"links\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yesterday evening , the Posada story was featured in the public television news show in Germany ( ARD , Tagesthemen ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"featured\", does the participant \"ARD\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He added that around 1,100 cartoons were submitted by participants from more than 60 countries and that more than 200 are on show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"added\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A woman walks into an Israeli restaurant in mid-day , eats , observes families with old people and children eating their lunch in the adjacent tables and pays the bill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"walks\", does the participant \"woman\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think he left the Nail out of the shoe as a excuse to come back and see you hey he may be your Prince charming ..\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Balance died in 2004 after a ' fall . '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"Balance\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We were booked at the Sheraton with a number of other out - of - town wedding guests .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"the first night i brought her home i did the sniffing under the door thing and left it at that .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brought\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"those\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"James J. Hoecker , the former Federal Energy Regulatory Commission chairman , defended making the December decision and also defended Winter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defended\", does the participant \"Hoecker\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Newsweek reported that a \" second wave \" involving biological attacks had been thwarted upon the arrest of Al Qaeda members who had been intended to provide logistical support .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"Newsweek\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they eat lots of grilled meat , chorizo , and such , with potatoes\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have a bit of experience watching the usual assembly line .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think it will help me very much in my role .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Enron continues to feel free to move me around at will .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"move\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Civet cats are trapped and placed in small cages inside darkened sheds , where the temperature is kept up to 110 F by fires .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"trapped\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The classes cover all age and skill ranges , with BALLROOM , LATIN , SEQUENCE , STREET , DISCO , LINE DANCING , BALLET , TAP & JAZZ .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cover\", does the participant \"ranges\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached are my resume and an addendum covering academic & consulting experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"resume\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had no problem with my delivery .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"problem\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They know that the American advent implies for them a demotion , and an elevation of the Shiites and Kurds , and they refuse to go quietly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refuse\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dessert was ... hmmm , that 's interesting , I do n't even remember dessert .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the participant \"dessert\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Derrick did a terrible job , was a complete jerk the entire time , and I had no warning as to the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Derrick\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I faxed comments to you on dash .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"faxed\", does the participant \"comments\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"That rejection got to the point that George Harrison kicked Yoko Ono in the Apple studios during the filming of Let it Be .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kicked\", does the participant \"Ono\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"involving\", does the participant \"children\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vomiting\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"'' There is much better tactical cooperation between our forces on both sides of the border , but the movement of Taliban still goes on both ways , '' he adds .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adds\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I suggest a \" blind draw \" on the teams , best ball not scramble on the golf , and as for the wager , no emails from the losing team for one week !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suggest\", does the participant \"draw\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A girl raises her hand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the participant \"hand\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Denial of the status of marriage to those who would freely accept its responsibilities creates legal and economic inequities and social injustice .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"creates\", does the participant \"Denial\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have the following suggestion for our company .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"suggestion\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Cities such as Falluja received special treatment from Saddam and enjoyed a disproportionate share of the country 's wealth and power .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"treatment\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He and his master dragged me to my room and held judgment upon me as a convicted traitress .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dragged\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"undermining\", does the participant \"Pakistan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"surgery\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was told to leave a restaurant because I ordered water with my meal ( apparently this is \" washing down \" your food \" ) and not ordering wine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The dramatic increase in radiation - induced thyroid cancers in children and adolescents in Belarus , Russia , and Ukraine , which have been observed since 1991 , continues to this day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continues\", does the participant \"increase\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"JUNO AND OPEN I LOVE YOU GUYS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LOVE\", does the participant \"YOU\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the participant \"horseman\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I got a coupon from Pennysaver for this station .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"coupon\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It is this circle that makes sure that women remain inferior , that democracy is unthinkable and that exposure to the outside world is minimal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"women\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They LOVE to climb .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LOVE\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We had a great stay , your service was excellent and we will use you again !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i satisfy your appetitie for lovin .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"satisfy\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a Saab ... which everything is expensive on and they have been extrememly fair and price a lot lower than any other shop I called .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Saab\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I spoke with Mike Collins [ 203-719-8385 ( phone ) and 203-719-7031 ( fax ) ] who conrfirmed to me that the cap included the remaining 2.5 + million remaining shares .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think she likes her special room in your house .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"oh god is there an agenda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"agenda\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He said Mr Dar , 33 , was arrested in Indian - administered Kashmir and belonged to the outlawed Lashkar - e - Toiba militant group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Dar\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"** Google defies US over search data **\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defies\", does the participant \"US\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The other stylists around me kept pressuring me saying he 's so wonderful , you 're going to love your hair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pressuring\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"With your help , we know she can do it !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have no doubt that the civilized world will prevail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"birdie\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Al - Iraqiyah tv said that ICDC were controlling Ramadi .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"tv\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sheriff 's deputies in Louisiana made a third arrest Wednesday in the ongoing investigation of a case involving allegations of sexual abuse of children and animals at a Ponchatoula , La. , church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"arrest\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe that these are three weekends in a row , January 6 , 13 and 20th .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We pointed out to the PX that there was excess credit .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pointed\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ended up paying much more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paying\", does the participant \"more\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The US chose to ally itself with such groups as the Supreme Council for the Islamic Revolution in Iraq , whose 15,000 - strong Badr Corps paramilitary was trained by the Iranian Revolutionary Guards .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ally\", does the participant \"itself\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I thought we only had cashout , at most 3 times , before this June .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The German Expressionist movement was destroyed as a result .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"destroyed\", does the participant \"movement\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attorney General Ashcroft explained that an \" either - or \" approach is not useful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"explained\", does the participant \"Ashcroft\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Previous reviewers said they were pushy and I can understand that , but I find the staff more helpful than anything else .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had a larger black population in the 70s than we have now but they did not have any power until Willie Brown was elected .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"elected\", does the participant \"Brown\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The next day , the federal commission killed the new pricing plan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"plan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Fried rice has NO flavor , it literally taste like water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rice\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I hope all are well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Biloxi , 30 people were reported dead in one block of flats which was hit by a 9 m ( 30 ft ) \" storm surge \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"people\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"okay .... I have a dog and my mother is really really terrified of hamsters .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My friend and I were to stay here for a girls night , catch up on our lives evening .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"were\", does the participant \"friend\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I guess that tells you a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"Saddam\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We came at around 730 and they close at 8 and wanted to try the specials but they were out for the day so I would say go way before they close .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"close\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I did the work myself for $ 50 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"work\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a kitten who just turned 3 months today .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"kitten\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"US - trained Malaysian biochemist Yazid Sufaat met with 9/11 plotters and two hijackers in January 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have wavy hair and she cut to my hair style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"pet\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" I do n't know how these events could have taken place without some concerted effort , \" said Dunn .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Dunn\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They chased the Communists out of the capital ( Hanoi ) and retook control .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"chased\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"yea i guess but rabbits a easily escape a pen or another rabbit could get in there and that rabbit could be the opposite gender .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Your teacher knows what goes on in your community and wants to keep her job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knows\", does the participant \"teacher\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The referenced TAGG # was entered as a ' New Counterparty ' , can you please let me know what counterparty this is so we can correctly assess the counterparty exposure .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assess\", does the participant \"exposure\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"One suspects that earlier reviewer works for another laundry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suspects\", does the participant \"One\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"they recovered the pics geeksquad deleted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recovered\", does the participant \"pics\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I love this place lots of people to talk to and school is across the street !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"place\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I worked with Andrew for 2 months and did acupuncture and herbs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"worked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In the third week I had more than $ 10,000.00 and it 's still growing !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They both had pools for kids and adults .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"pools\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe he must have waited among the gorse bushes through which the path winds and struck him down as he passed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"$\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( I think there are close to 24,000 groups )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It is rumored that North Korea has at least a couple nuclear weapons .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rumored\", does the participant \"It\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"requested\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have a customer for life in us !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"customer\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He eats all of his grain but it just takes him a while to get it chewed because of the lack of muscle in his jaws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eats\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"At 3:15 am on night # 2 , the fire alarm and strobe light activated in my room .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"activated\", does the participant \"alarm\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I want to go to the cafeteria for vegetables .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"These look fine to me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"look\", does the participant \"These\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Yes , they all have secret locator chips , just like gps\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"chips\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These guys do great work at VERY reasonable prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"do\", does the participant \"guys\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"they all need love and attn , food , proper surroundings etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It put hair on my chest and thanks to the owner s advice I invested vanguard , got myself a woman like Jerry , and became a republican .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"invested\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Mark Elliott tells me that you drafted some trader guidelines ( physical and financial ) for the London traders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"drafted\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They kill people .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"people\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I expect that many of the displaced people ( those affluent and those not ) will remain in the places they were evacuated to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Either I suck at my own style or Janice is a genius .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suck\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Just remember to make sure the mother is properly caring for the baby .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"caring\", does the participant \"mother\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Ash - Sharq al - Awsat reports that Fallujah was closed Tuesday in a general strike .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reports\", does the participant \"Awsat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I had my horse transported from CA to WA and he came on this big , open stock trailer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transported\", does the participant \"horse\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Any of the tip - top places have great ice - cream , get them to mix it up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cream\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I visited their huge Chicago lighting showroom and all I have to say is WOW !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"visited\", does the participant \"showroom\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Dunn believes the resulting overcharges for electricity exceeded $ 30 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceeded\", does the participant \"overcharges\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There are special regions uniquely and imposingly designed for the children .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"regions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached for your further handling is the draft form Deemed ISDA between ENA and Ispat Mexicana S.A. de C.V .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"form\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I found this on a bulletin board and decided to try it : I do n't care about the useless pre-fabricated crap this message usually says .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"China wanted an overland route through its own territory , which would give it ultimate control if hostilities broke out .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"route\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"After training , Bush kept flying , racking up hundreds of hours in F - 102 jets .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We had an inside cabin and it is what I would recommend .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It incorporates Mr. Stojic 's and Mr. Kelly 's initial comments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporates\", does the participant \"comments\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We are resolved that the State should not interfere with same - gender couples who choose to marry and share fully and equally in the rights , responsibilities , and commitments of civil marriage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interfere\", does the participant \"State\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We tried 4 different style of donuts , they were all the same when it came to quality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But he suffers the severe effects of the aftermath , and we are all suffering along with him now , since he is the most powerful man in the world .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suffers\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the participant \"Mobil\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He gave no indication on the value of the highest bid .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The difference is when the cat hisses , that means they are annoyed and they want the other cat to go away .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hisses\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Well you say Miramar I say Piramar\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I wanted to let you know about this before I respond to her request .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"respond\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I explained to him what I wanted and that I previously went to Braman Honda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"explained\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But my father 's former Iraqi business partner remained in control of the republic of Iraq and its petroleum reserves .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remained\", does the participant \"partner\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They fixed the queso !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Peter Dale Scott includes an account of how Terrell 's whistleblowing was stifled by them in his book Cocaine Politics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stifled\", does the participant \"whistleblowing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Another connection to Philippine terror and weapons smuggling - dating from the 1980s - is alleged in the book Disposable Patriot , by Jack Terrell .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"alleged\", does the participant \"connection\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I leave the evening of the 21st , my flight comes in about 10 pm , and leave the morning of the 27th at 6 am .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"leave\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I wanted to try someplace new again .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I promise you will not be disappointed !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"promise\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He refused to believe them and ordered the military to win the war within two to three years ( before the next election in 1968 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A pattern of arrests and seizures indicate that arms are brought by the LTTE from Laos , Cambodia and Thailand into Chittagong , from where they are transported northward by land to Bhutan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brought\", does the participant \"arms\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Allawi 's aged cousin and the man 's wife and daughter - in - law were abducted and guerrillas threaten to behead them if the Fallujah compaign is not stopped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threaten\", does the participant \"guerrillas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemned\", does the participant \"murder\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They offer an exceptional compensation package including a healthy salary , comprehensive benefits program , and ample room for associates to grow within the firm .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grow\", does the participant \"associates\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have a question about McDonald 's Monopoly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Success comes before work \" only in the dictionary\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comes\", does the participant \"Success\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He needs more info about these trades ( i.e. , price info ) and would like to talk with you about it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"needs\", does the participant \"info\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have 4 Golden Wonder Killifish .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"Alexander\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I called the front desk and got no answer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"desk\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I doubt he will be extradited to Venezuela , which is the only way that question could be answered with a Yes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extradited\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Some board members pushed to have Winter removed , but there were concerns such action would lead to more chaos , the governor 's spokesman Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"Winter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I want signed and numbered .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I talked with Mark at SW Gas - just honro his numbers\"\nQuestion: In the event \"talked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Radical Shiite cleric Muqtada al - Sadr said the attack was \" criminal \" and that \" the Zionists have left only one choice for the Arabs , that of fighting and jihad \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Sadr\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I bought a beginner s quilling set and like making the filigree forms you can make and add to other crafts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought it would pass until he started to vomit blood and would nt drink any water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have to tell you that I have n't had one and do n't want one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They wish to launch on Sept. 1 - meaning we will need to be sending mailings sometime around mid-August .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They want to use LTS to tie into NASA 's vision for Space Exploration , and seem pleased that the White House is moving in that direction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The S100 has a slightly larger screen and the new digic 5 processor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"screen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Allawi 's aged cousin and the man 's wife and daughter - in - law were abducted and guerrillas threaten to behead them if the Fallujah compaign is not stopped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"abducted\", does the participant \"cousin\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He was warned that they were building up a huge Army and would eventually launch an attack , but he ignored his military advisers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ignored\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You have to bring in your own models and they have to pay for you to use them if you do nt then you can graduate !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"graduate\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Two vaunted economists - one a Nobel Prize winner and the other a nationally renowned budget expert - have analyzed the data at hand and put a price tag on the Iraq occupation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"economists\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The work was completed within one week , and everything was cleaned up on completion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"completed\", does the participant \"work\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My boyfriend and I were woken up in the middle of the night at our campsite by drunken kids who 'd arrived around 1:00 am and were drinking at the springs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"woken\", does the participant \"boyfriend\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The doctor 's office said that payments had been \" reversed \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"office\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I encourage you to do this dance , as it has tremendous positive effects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encourage\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In the medium case , investigations find that Enron ( like others ) \" played by the rules , \" but the rules stunk , and Enron profited at the expense of California consumers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"played\", does the participant \"Enron\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have a 4 months Shih Tzu puppy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"India 's Andaman and Nicobar Islands comprise more than 500 islands lying 1,000 kilometers east of Sri Lanka in the Bay of Bengal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comprise\", does the participant \"Islands\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Upon the same day he conquered Darius , won a great victory at sea , & died the same day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"conquered\", does the participant \"Darius\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You want your dog to admire you as his pack leader , not fear you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"admire\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Both Dawa and SCIRI have umbilical connections to the fundamentalist Shi'ite leadership in Iran that go back decades .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Dawa\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The islamists sent letter bombs in January 1997 to newspaper offices in New York City and Washington , D.C. .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"bombs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Pound for pound , mountain lions eat more game and more livestock than wolves .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"game\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A NATO spokesman said : \" There 's no tracking mechanism to ensure they do n't fall into the wrong hands .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fall\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: \n", "correct_value": "No"}]